Houba Vincent

I am a fullstack developer with equal knowledge on the front and backend side.

I am a quick learner, I work with a lot of different thecnologies lanuages, library, frameworks.

I can Build static website, spa, mobile application, cli, create rest

api, work with sql and no-sql database deploy in cloud (aws)

My language of expertise are python (django, flask, aiohttp) and javascript (react, vue)

I am also a lisp hacker, emacs guru and a git ninja

Experience

Front end engineering - (Robovision) - (June 2018 - April 2019) - (Belgium/Ghent)

- Create multiple tools to label images
- · Build charts and metrics for quality of labeling
- Merge quasar (vue framework) version to more recent one
- Create multiple reusable component.
- Create an admin to create projects, users, group...
- Test components with cypress
- Python, Vue, Vuex, Vue-router, Quasar, Typescript, Es6, cypress, Docker

Full Stack Developer - (Factory) - (Aout 2017 - May 2018) - (Belgium/Liege)

P-heal

- Working on an iot device that calculate weight variations and blinking to help people take theirs medicaments
- Create a mobile application with react-native for the p-heal device
- Refactor the backend to aws with serverless

Big Data Media

- Create a recommendation engine for a broadcaster.
- Built a microservice to extract content from video.
- Test the recommendation engine with unitetest and behave.
- Searching for solution to improve the recommendation engine (tf/idf, elasticsearch).
- Create a cache system with redis to avoid collecting and fetching the same data.
- Collect data on users (time spended on article, time spend watching a video...) to rate articles and videos.
- Python, kafka, aiohttp, sql, behave, unittest, react, docker, redis, pyspark, pandas

Full Stack Developer - (Vesperia) - (June 2016 - Aout 2017) - (Luxembourg)

Doctena

Render their mail responsive with ljml

- Improve their javascript code base mainly angular and jquery
- Resolve visual bugfix

Logdirect

- Refactor front end code for different site, with jquery, gulp, css
- Unittest made home framework with nodejs

atHome

• Bulding static analyse tools with typescript (made home framework)

Education

Aug 2014-May 2015

Java cloud computing; STE-Formations(Liege)

- Learning advanced design pattern in java
- Algorithm course on paper
- database analyse and creation
- Advanced sql with postgresql (view, trigger, creating function) psql
- Building a sudoku

Aug 2012-May 2014

Bac+2 Web developer; IPSF(Liege)

- Learning html, css, jquery, php, mysql, wordpress (first year)
- learning poo, symfony2, version control (second year)
- Building website for asbl in symfony2 (second year)
- Creating a site for lawfirm with python(django) (final)

Skills

- Languages:
 - Python 5
 - Javascript (es6) 4
 - Typescript 3
 - Ruby 3
 - Bash 2
 - Node 2
 - Elisp 2
 - Elixir 2
 - Clojure 2
 - Php 1
 - Java 1
- Framework python:
 - Django 3
 - Flask 3
 - Nikola 2
 - Aiohttp 1
- Framework javascript:

- Vue 4
- Quasar 4
- React 3
- Redux 3
- React native 3
- Gatsby 3
- Jquery 2
- Angular 2
- Integrations:
 - Css 3
 - Stylus 3
 - Bulma 3
 - Sass 2
 - Foundation 2
 - Bootstrap 2
 - Materialize 2
- Build tools:
 - Webapck 3
 - Brunch 2
 - Gulp 2
 - Grunt 2
- Servers:
 - Nginx 2
 - Apache 2
- Databases:
 - Postgresql 3
 - Mysql 2
 - Sqlite 2
 - Mongo 2
 - Redis 3
 - Dynamodb 3
- Tools:
 - Emacs 5
 - Git 4
 - Aws 3
 - Docker 3
 - Google cloud 2
 - Vagrant 2
 - Jira 2
 - Gitlab 3
 - Github 2
 - Bitbucket 2
 - Jenkins 2
- Os:
 - Ubuntu 3
 - Debian 3
 - Arch 3

Redhat 1

Extra

- Languages:
 - French (native speaker)
 - English (excellent)
- hobbies
 - Webscraping, Machine learning, Game creation
 - Reading
 - Proxy http trafics from my webbrowser and try to understand what's going on

houbavince@gmail.com • +32499316385 • 29 years old

Quai de l'ourthe n 22 tilff - Liege, Belgium

Website: https://silly-mclean-010d02.netlify.com/cv